(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-02T23:54:18.196182",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
えー、みなちゃま、
Um, everyone...
本日は、轟はじめ生誕祭2026
today, for Todoroki Hajime's 2026 Birthday Celebration
「Rise in motion」にお越しくださいまして
"Rise in motion," thank you so much
誠にありがとうございます。
for coming today.
開演に先立ちまして、みなちゃまにお願いと
Prior to the start of the performance, I have some
ご案内を申し上げます。
requests and announcements for you all.
えー、当配信は一部収録を含みますが、
This stream includes some pre-recorded content,
生配信部分もございますので、
but there are also live broadcast sections,
いっぱいコメントして盛り上げてください！
so please send lots of comments to liven things up!
今もね、じわーっていっぱい「こんちくわ」とか
They're pouring in right now! Lots of "Konchikuwa,"
「きちゃ」やパチパチ、ありがとうございます。
"It's here!" and clapping. Thank you so much!
えー、当配信のハッシュタグは、
The hashtag for this stream is
「#轟はじめ生誕祭2026」です。
"#TodorokiHajimeBirthdayCelebration2026".
SNSでたくさんポストしていただけると嬉しいです。
I'd love it if you posted a lot on social media.
開演中はカメラやスマートフォンでの写真撮影大歓迎なので、
Photos using cameras or smartphones are welcome during the show,
たくさんポストして盛り上げていただけると幸いです。
so please post lots of them to keep the excitement going.
それでは、開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Well then, please wait a little longer for the show to start.
えー、みなちゃま、
Um, everyone...
本日は、轟はじめ生誕祭2026
today, for Todoroki Hajime's 2026 Birthday Celebration
「Rise in motion」にお越しくださいまして
"Rise in motion," thank you so much
誠にありがとうございます。パート2！
for coming today. Part 2!
どれどれ？何かグダグダしてなさそうですね、みなちゃま。
Let's see... everything seems to be going smoothly, everyone.
うおーって、わくわく、こんちくわ、と、大丈夫そうです。
Lots of "Woah," "excitement," and "Konchikuwa," so we're good!
開演に先立ちまして、みなちゃまにお願いとご案内を、もう一回申し上げます。
Prior to the start, let me repeat the requests and announcements once more.
当配信は一部収録を含みますが、
This stream includes some pre-recorded content,
生配信部分もございますので、
but there are also live broadcast sections,
いっぱいコメントして盛り上げていただけると嬉しいです。
so I'd love it if you commented a lot to keep the excitement going.
きちゃ！大丈夫ちょ パート2！きちゃ！ありがとう！
I'm here! "Daijobu Cho" Part 2! I'm here! Thank you!
えー、超配信のハッシュタグは、ハッシュタグ「轟はじめ生誕祭2026」です！
Um, the hashtag for today's stream is #TodorokiHajimeSeitansai2026!
SNSでたくさんポストしてください！
Please post a lot on social media!
えー、開演中は、えー、カメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影大歓迎です！
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone during the show is highly welcomed!
たくさんポストして盛り上げていただけると嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if you post a lot and liven things up!
それでは、えー、開演まで、えー、今しばらく、おまちくださーい！
Now then, please wait a little longer until the show begins!
バンザイ 無能な命に
Banzai, to this incompetent life...
くだらないよ 紛い物だってば ラリアッチュー
It's worthless, even if it's just an imitation, lariat-chu!
喝采 消し去るような もん
It's like erasing all the applause.
不条理 浴びながら 僕は home
While being showered in absurdity, I head home.
才能は ゼロ どうにかしちまちょってるけど
My talent is zero, I've messed up somehow, but...
歓声は no だっての
The cheers are a "no", I say.
愛にもたれた 言葉で 心拍数
Heart rate spikes at words leaning on love.
生きてく程 胸は 沈んでゆく
The more I live, the deeper my heart sinks.
どーなってんだろーな？この動画
I wonder what's going on with this video...
かいつまんでも しょうがねぇ
Summarizing it does no good.
汗かき 稼ぐ お金は どんだけ？
How much money do I earn sweating?
あーだこーだ そんなもんか 五月蠅（うるせ）えわな
This and that, is that all? So annoying.
バンザイ 無能な命に
Banzai, to this incompetent life...
から回ってく脳を 満たしてくれ
Please fill my spinning brain.
未来予想図なんか描けない
I can't draw any plans for the future.
くだらないよ 紛い物だって それ
It's worthless, even if it's just an imitation.
半端者なら やれない ナリじゃん
If you're halfway, you can't act the part.
朱色になって 僕は思い通り
Turning vermilion, I have my way.
太陽系で巣食った罵詈雑言 インベーダー
The solar system nested with abuse, invader.
足が止まってる シューゲイザー 死にそうでも ギリですか？
Feet frozen, shoegazer, are you barely surviving?
のらりくらり 躱すわ 初めまして カミサマ
Dodging listlessly, nice to meet you, God.
もし 救われる のなら 腹切るわ 今から
If I'm to be saved, I'll commit hara-kiri right now.
get down get down 揺らめく
Get down, get down, wavering...
get down get down
乗り込んだ Twitter 空間が
Entering the Twitter space...
君を狂わしてんだ
It's driving you crazy.
滅多なもんじゃ おどろかねぇ
I won't be surprised by just anything.
汗かき 生きた 最期も あっけねぇ
Living sweating, even the end is anti-climactic.
虚しいわな
How empty indeed.
バンザイ 無能な
Banzai, to this incompetent...
A INNOCENCE
絡まってく脳を満たしてくれ
Fill up my tangled brain
未来予想図なんかかき消せ
Erase any plans for the future
くだらない夢買い戻したってそれ
Even if we buy back foolish dreams, so what?
中途半端なものならやれない Mary Jane
If it's half-hearted, I can't do it, Mary Jane
お化けになって 没は思い通り
Become a ghost, let the rejected plans go as they will
パリラ ここはきっと奈落だ
Parira, this place is surely hell
声にもならぬ声が
A voice that doesn't sound like a voice
腹の底からせり上がるんだ 「ダメ！それ！」
Rises from the pit of my stomach, "No! Stop!"
押し殺す本能
The stifled instinct
ユラユラ鈍色の海から
Swaying from the dark gray sea,
幽列車と雲ヶ島
the ghost train and cloud island
ただただ君は呟くんだ
you only mutter,
「人は怖いね」と
"People are scary, aren't they?"
今 弾ける七色
Now, seven bursting colors
アイアイアイアイ 宙を舞って踊り散らすの
Aye aye aye aye, dancing and scattering in the air
ファッションビートで気取って
Striking a pose to the fashion beat,
チンケな狂人ぶるんじゃない
don't pretend to be a cheap lunatic.
報われない悲しみ食らってこう
Let's feed on unrewarded sadness.
ファッションビートに染まって
Dyed by the fashion beat,
言うことないなら息しても
if there's nothing to say, even if you breathe,
無駄だ アイヤイヤイヤ 笑え少年よ
it's a waste. Aye ya ya ya, laugh, oh boy!
ええじゃないか ええじゃないか
Why not? Why not?
この先は何もわからんし
Who knows what lies ahead anyway?
無礼じゃないか 無礼じゃないか
Isn't it rude? Isn't it rude?
クソッタレ見てられん煩脳
Damn it, I can't stand to look at these worldly desires
ああ 荒れ狂う世の中だから
Ah, because it's a wild and crazy world,
アイアイアイアイ 宙を舞って終わりにするの
Aye aye aye aye, so let's dance in the air and end it
ファッションビートで気取って
Striking a pose to the fashion beat,
チンケな狂人ぶるんじゃない
don't pretend to be a cheap lunatic.
報われない悲しみ食らってこう
Let's feed on unrewarded sadness.
ファッションビートに染まって
Dyed by the fashion beat,
言うことないなら息しても
if there's nothing to say, even if you breathe,
無駄だ アイヤイヤイヤ 笑え少年よ
it's a waste. Aye ya ya ya, laugh, oh boy!
絵に描いたようなストーリー 僕の色を塗れぬほどに落ちぶれた
A picture-perfect story, I fell so low I couldn't paint my color
モノクロに過ぎる日を 乗り越えられたら
If I can get through the days that pass by in monochrome...
ああ 今夜は笑って あの幽列車にキスをして
Ah, laugh tonight, kiss that ghost train,
七色に生まれ変わるのさ
and be reborn in seven colors
ファッションビートに染まって
Dyed by the fashion beat,
言うことないなら息しても
if there's nothing to say, even if you breathe,
無駄だ アイヤイヤイヤ 笑え少年よ
it's a waste. Aye ya ya ya, laugh, oh boy!
あぁー！楽しー！
Ah! That was fun!
やっぱ歌って踊るの楽しー！
Singing and dancing is definitely so fun!
いぇーい！いぇーい！やったー！
Yay! Yay! I did it!
ちょっとぶちかまっちゃったんですけど、すいません！
I went a bit wild, but sorry about that!
なんか番長とかやってたんですか？
Was someone playing Bancho or something?
え？お？なんか、なんか撮ってました？
Eh? Oh? Was someone filming something?
え、なんか撮ってましたよね？
Wait, someone was filming, right?
え、ていうか、なんかこれ配信されてますこれ！？
Wait, is this streaming? Is this being streamed right now?!
えー！？ちょっと待って！著作権とかあるんですけど、はじめにも！
What?! Wait, wait a minute! Even Hajime has copyrights, you know!
な、な、なんかコメントがすごい流れてるんですけど、
The comments are going really fast, but...
反転してて読めません！
They're mirrored so I can't read them!
え、ちょ、なんか、ぱちぱちちって、拍手してくれてて、
Ah, wait, it looks like everyone is clapping...
なんか、かっこよちぎって、何や？
And... "too cool"? What does that mean?
え、すごい、なんか、え？え、く、く、なんか、草生やされた。
Wow, wait, what? Ah... they are posting "lol".
え、なんか、なんか、ありがとうございます。えっ、
Uh, thank you so much! Um...
ハッシュタグ、ばんじょの生誕祭2026で、なんか、たくさんポストしてくれてるみたいなんですけど、
It seems like you're posting a lot with the hashtag #BanchoBirthday2026...
何だろ、このタグ。わかんないけど、
I wonder what this tag is. I don't really know, but...
はじめ、お祝いしてもらってるし、ポスト、してくれたら、嬉しいかも。
Hajime is being celebrated, so I'd be happy if you post under it!
ありがとう。
Thank you!
え、やっとはじめ、歌ったり踊ったりとか、するの好きで、
Ah, finally... Hajime loves singing and dancing,
本当はこう、たくさんの人の前でパフォーマンスすることに、憧れて、
and I've always dreamed of performing in front of a big crowd.
ちょっと、上京したいな、とか思ってるんですけど、
I've been thinking about moving to Tokyo,
ちょっと、勇気が出なくて、
but I couldn't build up the courage...
うー、えっ？
Uh, wait...
はじめなら大丈夫？行ける？
"You'll be fine, Hajime"? "You can do it"?
え、コメントの方達はどう思ってる？
What do you guys in the comments think?
可愛い、なんて？なんか、思って、あっ、ダンスうま！
"Cute," "What?" Ah, "Good dancer!"
すごい褒められてる！あっ、かっこいい！褒められてる！
I'm getting praised so much! Ah, "Cool!" I'm being praised!
よし！じゃあ、皆さんにすごい勇気をもらったので、はじめ、
Alright! You've given me so much courage, so Hajime...
行ってきます！夢を目指して、上京してくる！
is going! I'm moving to the city to chase my dream!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
荒れ狂う季節の中を
In the season of storms
二人は一人きり　さらり
The two of us are alone, easily
明け行く夕日の中を
In the dawning sunset
今夜も昼下がり　さらり
Tonight it is early afternoon, easily
どれほど朽ち果てようと
No matter how much we decay
最後には笑いたい
I want to laugh at the end
何のために戦おうとも
No matter what you are fighting for
動機は愛がいい
The motivation should be love
新しい日々は探さずとも常にここに
New days are always here, even if you don't look for them
色々見てきたけれどこの瞳は永遠に
I've seen so many things, but these eyes will forever be
きらり
sparkling
あれほど生きてきたけれど
I've lived so long
全ては夢みたい
But everything is like a dream
あれもこれも魅力的でも
Everything and anything is attractive
私は君がいい
But I prefer you
どこにいたの　探してたよ
Where have you been? I was looking for you
連れてって　連れてって
Take me, take me
何もかも　捨ててくよ
I will throw everything away
どこまでも　どこまでも
Wherever you go, wherever you go
荒れ狂う季節の中も
In the raging season
群衆の中も
In the crowd
君とならば　さらり　さらり
If I'm with you, it's smooth, smooth
新しい日々も　拙い過去も
New days and the clumsy past
全てがきらり
Everything is sparkling
無くしてしまったものを振り返って
Looking back on what I lost
ほろり
I shed a tear
時には途方に暮れてただ風に吹かれて
Sometimes I feel lost and just sway in the wind
ゆらり
swaying
息せき切ってきたの
I came running out of breath
行き先は決めたの
I decided where I was going
迷わずに行きたいけど保証はしないよ
I want to go without hesitation, but I can't guarantee it
何か分かったようで
It feels like I understand something
何も分かってなくて
But I understand nothing
だけどそれが分かって本当に良かった
But I'm really glad I realized that
何か分かった 本当に良かった
I understood something, and I'm truly glad.
新しい日々は 探さずとも常にここにある ここに ここに
New days are always right here, even without searching. Right here, right here...
あれ程に色々見てきたけれど この瞳は変わり切らない 永遠に きらり
Though I have seen so much, these eyes won't change. Forever shining...
生きていくけれど 全ては夢みたい
I go on living, but everything feels like a dream.
誰も彼も魅力的なの でも私は君がいい
Everyone is charming, but you are the one for me.
どこに行ったの
Where did you go?
探していたよ
I was looking for you.
連れてって 連れてって
Take me with you, take me with you.
何もかも 捨てていくよ
I will leave everything behind.
どこまでも どこまでも
Wherever it takes us, wherever it takes us.
荒れ狂う季節の中も 群衆の中も
Even in the raging seasons, and in the crowd...
君とならば さらり さらり
With you, it's so smooth, so easy.
新しい日々も 拙い過去も
The new days, and the clumsy past...
全てがきらり
Everything is shining.
Welcome to our theater ほら 踊れば
Welcome to our theater! Look, once we dance,
幕開けの合図が calling you back
the signal of the curtain raising is calling you back.
月火から水木にお疲れ everybody clap your hands
Good job getting through Monday to Thursday, everybody clap your hands.
待ち侘びた金土日さ come and bring all your friends
Friday, Saturday, Sunday we've waited for is here, come and bring all your friends.
世間は work work 目線は don't stop 心も体もボロボロです
The world is work, work; our gaze is don't stop; our minds and bodies are worn down.
頑張り屋な日本人に everybody clap your hands
To the hardworking Japanese people, everybody clap your hands.
やるせない朝にうんざりしちゃって
Feeling so fed up with those depressing mornings...
何も変わんない routine 染み込んだ癖
A routine where nothing changes, a habit soaked in.
ミステイクまた自分のせいに 憧れ持ったお天気
Blaming myself for mistakes again, and the carefree weather I longed for...
結局はいつも通りだ
In the end, it's just business as usual.
過ぎ去っていく day by day
Passing by day by day.
考えたって don't know if it's the right way
Even if I think about it, I don't know if it's the right way.
吹く風も味方にして let's ride away
Let's turn even the blowing wind to our side, and let's ride away.
Welcome to our theater ほら 踊れば
Welcome to our theater! Look, once we dance,
幕開けの合図が it's calling you back
the signal of the curtain raising is calling you back.
波瀾万丈な人生くらいがちょうどいいのさ
A life full of ups and downs is just about perfect.
君が創るショータイムを見せて 見せて
Show me, show me the showtime that you create.
ちょうだい
Give it to me.
春夏すぎ秋冬にやれやれ everybody clap your hands
Spring and summer have passed, now it's autumn and winter, oh dear, everybody clap your hands.
ギリギリ駆け込んで間に合うかの never ending game
Rushing in at the last minute, wondering if we'll make it in this never-ending game.
気持ちは go go されども no no 現実はそう甘くないね
My feelings are go, go, but still, no, no, reality isn't that sweet, is it?
働き者な日本人に everybody clap your hands
To the hardworking Japanese people, everybody clap your hands.
お決まりの suit and tie how can I be myself and I
In the usual suit and tie, how can I be myself and I?
どれもこれも色のない世界には興味ない
I have no interest in this world where everything is colorless.
見る向こう側で we're gonna find a way
On the other side of what we see, we're gonna find a way.
Welcome to our theater ほら 踊れば
Welcome to our theater! Look, once we dance,
幕開けの合図が it's calling you back
the signal of the curtain raising is calling you back.
波瀾万丈な人生くらいがちょうどいいのさ
A life full of ups and downs is just about perfect.
君が創るショータイムを見せて 見せて
Show me, show me the showtime that you create.
過ぎ去っていく day by day
Passing by day by day.
考えたって don't know if it's the right way
Even if I think about it, I don't know if it's the right way.
吹く風も味方にして let's ride away
Let's turn even the blowing wind to our side, and let's ride away.
Welcome to our theater ほら 踊れば
Welcome to our theater! Look, once we dance,
幕開けの合図が it's calling you back
the signal of the curtain raising is calling you back.
波瀾万丈な人生くらいがちょうどいいのさ
A life full of ups and downs is just about perfect.
君が創るショータイムを見せて 見せて
Show me, show me the showtime that you create.
とびきりショータイム 誰でも招待
An extraordinary showtime, everyone is invited!
あなたのショータイムを見せて ちょうだい
Show me your showtime, please.
とびきりショータイム 誰でも招待
An extraordinary showtime, everyone is invited!
あなたのショータイムを見せて ちょうだい
Show me your showtime, please.
えっ、あ、にょ！星街すいちゃんですよにょ？
Eh, ah, nyo! Are you Hoshimachi Suisei-chan, nyo?
ご存じかしら？ありがとう
Do you know of me? Thank you.
えっ、あ、にょ、なんか、超偶然出ちゃったけど…
Eh, ah, nyo, somehow it was a total coincidence, but...
こうやって一緒に歌えて嬉しかったでしょう？
You were happy that we got to sing together like this, right?
私も嬉しかったわ
I was happy too.
わあ、嬉しい！すいちゃん！
Wow, I'm so glad! Sui-chan!
ありがとう
Thank you.
え、でも、でも、あの、このシアター、勝手に入っていいんですか？
Um, but, but, is it really okay for us to just enter this theater?
まあ、ダメかもしれないわね
Well, it might actually not be allowed.
ダメなの？！
It's not allowed?!
うん
Yeah.
え、じゃあ怒られる、怒られる
Wait, then we'll get scolded, we'll get scolded!
まあ、怒られるわね
Well, we will definitely get scolded.
何でここ連れてきてくれたんですか？！
Then why did you bring me here?!
あそこの人がもう銃構えてるわ、こうやって
That person over there is already aiming a gun, like this.
怖い、怖い！
Scary, scary!
えっ、そんな、物騒なものがあるんですか？
Wait, is there really something that dangerous here?
あ、違う違う。あの、この人、オーディション出場者で...
Ah, no, no. You see, this person is an audition contestant...
え？
Eh?
オーディション、ここでオーディションやってるんで、オーディション出場者、出場者ってことにしよう、ね
They're holding auditions here, so let's pretend we're audition contestants, okay?
なんでこっち...
Why are you looking over here...
そう、そう。ここでオーディションやってるんだ
Right, right. They're holding auditions here.
受けたほうがいいんじゃない？ね？
Shouldn't you try auditioning? Right?
たちかわ？
Tachikawa?
じゃないと撃たれる、撃たれる！
Otherwise you'll get shot, you'll get shot!
怖い！怖いよー
Scary! That's scary!
撃たれるよ、ねえ
You'll get shot, you know.
あれ、星街すいせいじゃない！？
Hey, isn't that Hoshimachi Suisei?!
あ、あれ？あれ？あ！
Ah, oh? Oh?
あれ？いけね、じゃあねー！
Oh? Oops, gotta go, see ya!
えっ、ちょ、えっ、やばい！ええー？
Wait, what, whoa, this is bad! Ehhh?
あれ？ええー？どっちや？
Huh? Ehhh? Which way?
はあ...
Sigh...
ステップはお静かに
[Song: Steps Silently]
Stealthな奪い取りの Party party jam
A stealthy heist party, party jam,
抜き足差し足 あら息潜め劇場
stealthy footsteps, oh, a breathless theater.
Step by step 焦らない 教えるわ
Step by step, don't rush, I'll teach you.
心の赴くまま 胸躍らせて
Following your heart's desire, make your chest leap.
強気な瞳 隠して
Hide your confident gaze,
少しずつ 近づき 笑って
approach step by step, and smile.
上品な蹴り 蹴り上げ
An elegant high kick,
システムをちょっと誤解させて
confusing the security system for a moment,
仕留めてあげるわ
and I will finish you off.
Stealthな同じダンス ばっかりじゃ駄目
Dancing the exact same way all the time is no good.
Feel like もう一人の自分に勝つの
I feel like defeating my other self.
だって盗まれたら取り返すのが基本
After all, if it's stolen, the rule is to take it back.
タッグに合図して 静かにアシスト
Signal your partner for a silent assist,
ひらりと躱して逃げ切るのよ
swiftly dodge and make a clean getaway.
するりと手には超高級ジェム
Slipping into your hands is a super premium gem,
華麗に無音の逃走劇
a splendid, silent escape drama.
静かにちょっと誤解させて
Quietly confusing them for a moment,
仕留めてあげるわ
and I will finish you off.
Stealthな奪い返し Party party jam
A stealthy payback party, party jam,
抜き足差し足 あら息潜め劇場
stealthy footsteps, oh, a breathless theater.
Step by step 焦らない そのまま踊るのよ
Step by step, don't rush, keep dancing like that.
ずっとついておいでね
Follow me all the way,
踏み出してみてよ
try taking a step forward.
ここで決めるの
This is where we decide it,
誰も疑いはしないわ
no one will ever suspect a thing.
胸に秘めた宝石と
Keep that gem hidden in your chest,
静かに踊って
and dance quietly.
静かに踊ってよ
Yes, dance quietly,
ステップはお静かに
and keep your steps silent.
Dressing Room A
BAD HATTER
[Song: BAD HATTER]
Switching 何に塗れてJack コグがカチカンカン
Switching, what are you smeared in, Jack? Cogs ticking clank-clank,
Tapするガランドウ
tapping the hollow space.
超お洒落な帽子とステッキでナビゲート
Navigate with an ultra-stylish hat and cane
Step inside 最後のルナティック すでに紅揚 執着 Grab your souls
Step inside, the final lunatic, already high and clinging, grab your souls!
さあ乾杯しなキャバレー 今はこの欲望に溺れよう
So let's raise a glass, cabaret, drown in this greed for now!
遊限なら夜が明ける前まで
If it's a limited play, until the dawn comes...
味わい尽くすべき
You should taste it to the fullest.
You have Bad Hatter 親愛なるモンスター
You have Bad Hatter, my dear monster.
We are Bad Hatter 目線も退場もナンセンス
We are Bad Hatter, even the glance and exit are nonsense.
Bam Bam Moonlight 渋滞のダンスフロア
Bam Bam Moonlight, congested dance floor.
We are stakeholder 狂騒に飲まれ踊れ
We are stakeholders, get swallowed by the frenzy and dance!
脱字 惨事 アビエーション 常に空中飛び交う狂言堂
Omissions, disasters, aberration, always flying through the midair theater of falsehoods!
甲斐性ないなら秒でパス 老いも若きも等しく騙り合う
If you have no resourcefulness, pass in seconds, young and old alike deceive each other equally!
Step inside 最後のルナティック 誰も彼もが耳打ち クラシックトーク
Step inside, the final lunatic, everyone whispering classic talk.
一緒にどうですお嬢さん 素顔剥がした紳士がシャウトダンス
How about together, young lady? The gentleman who stripped off his real face shouts and dances!
幽霊だとかどんな見た目だろうが
Whether a ghost or whatever appearance it might be,
気にする暇もない
there's no time to even care!
You have Bad Hatter 親愛なるモンスター
You have Bad Hatter, my dear monster.
We are Bad Hatter 目線も退場もナンセンス
We are Bad Hatter, even the glance and exit are nonsense..
Bam Bam Moonlight 渋滞のダンスフロア
Bam Bam Moonlight, congested dance floor.
We are stakeholder 狂騒に飲まれ踊れ
We are stakeholders, get swallowed by the frenzy and dance!
ダバダバダビディディディデュダダディビディビドゥドゥディディディルル
Daba daba dabididididuda dabidibidududididiruru...
ドゥビダバドゥギャダドゥダドゥドゥバビディダルダディビドゥ
Dubidabadugyadadududubabididarudadibidu...
チャチャチャチャチャチャチャトッタチャチャチャチャチャチャパダドゥ
Chachachachachachatottachachachachachachapadadu...
アルバリドゥタラドゥタラドゥバドゥバディダダディビバビデドゥ
Arubaridutaradutaradubadubadidadadibibabidedu...
You have Bad Hatter 親愛なるモンスター
You have Bad Hatter, my dear monster.
We are Bad Hatter 目線も退場もナンセンス
We are Bad Hatter, even the glance and exit are nonsense.
Bam Bam Moonlight 渋滞のダンスフロア
Bam Bam Moonlight, congested dance floor.
We are stakeholder 狂騒に飲まれ踊れ
We are stakeholders, get swallowed by the frenzy and dance!
うぉ！おいちっちゃいの、何持ってんの？
Whoa! Hey, tiny one, what are you holding?
お？バツ？
Eh? An 'X'?
バツってどういうこと？も、もしかして…王莉ちゃんの審査員だったの？
An 'X'? What does that mean? C-Could it be... you were O-ri's judge?
ひょ、だってさっき、なんかノリノリで「ダバダバ…」ってやってたじゃん！
B-But just now, you were totally getting into it and doing the "daba-daba..." thing!
え？手品って？何だよ！王莉頑張ったよ！
Eh? Magic trick? What do you mean! O-ri worked hard!
ちょっと！ちょっと手品って！ねえ！
Wait, what magic trick? Hey!
あれ？あれ？
Huh? Huh?
なんか…体が…動かないんだけど…
Somehow... my body... won't move...
よっ…、なんか話しかけてもダメみたいだ…
Looks like speaking to them does no good either...
なんだよ！こっちから願い下げだ！こんな、こんな地下、出てってやる！
Whatever! I'm rejecting you first! I'm getting the hell out of this basement!
出られた…出られたよ…
I got out... I actually got out...
何見てんだよ！見んじゃねえ！
What are you looking at! Don't look at me!
うわっ…うぅ…うそ…
Whoa... Uh... No way...
脳震盪オブラート能天気どうかして
Brain concussion, sugar-coating, easygoing, is something wrong with you?
お淑やか失礼して 私的にお手製ね
Pardon my lack of grace, it's my own personal handiwork.
誠実度頂戴 ミスエゴイストどうかして
Give me your sincerity, Miss Egoist, what is wrong with you?
真偽不明なんて正気じゃない
Unconfirmed truth is simply insane.
夜はオンナンナンナノン
The night is on-nan-nan-nan-non.
僕らオンナンナンナンデン
We are on-nan-nan-nan-den.
針は針はコンパス 吸って吐いてジャッジメント
The needle is a compass, breathe in, breathe out, judgment.
宵闇コンパレート結構です
Twilight comparator, no thank you.
皆様ナンセンス はなはだナンセンス
Everyone is nonsense, utterly nonsense.
切るなかれ 黙れ 黙れ
Do not cut it, shut up, shut up!
この世はナンセンス 誠にカオス
This world is nonsense, truly chaos.
血の毒で暴れ暴れ仕方ない
Raging with blood poison, it can't be helped.
ほら先生引っ張って 行ってらっしゃい閻魔によろしく
Look, teacher, drag them along, have a safe trip, say hello to Enma for me.
言っといて
Tell him that.
気は病んでオブラート覚醒期どうかして
Mind is sick, sugar-coated, arousal period, is something wrong?
名義不明だとしても参りたい
Even if the name is unknown, I want to join.
僕ら...
We are...
まさに宣言通り
...exactly as declared,
ラットパトラン
Ratpatrun,
右も左もどんづまり
dead ends to the left and right.
ふざけたチェックメイト
A ridiculous checkmate.
ようやく今晩 無礼講決定
Finally tonight, we decide on no formalities.
召せよ ナンセンス
Feast on the nonsense,
はなはだナンセンス
highly nonsensical.
生きる流れに
In the flow of life,
だまれ だまれ だまれ
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
この世は ナンセンス
This world is nonsense.
誠に遺憾です
Truly regrettable,
気の毒ね
How pitiful.
暴れ 暴れ 暴れ
Go wild, go wild, go wild!
Can't you understand?
Yeah yeah yeah...
召せよ ナンセンス
Feast on the nonsense,
はなはだナンセンス
highly nonsensical.
生きる流れに
In the flow of life,
だまれ だまれ だまれ
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
この世は ナンセンス
This world is nonsense,
はなからナンセンス
nonsense from the start.
生きる流れに
In the flow of life,
だまれ だまれ だまれ
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
まもなく遺憾です
Shortly regrettable,
誠に遺憾です
truly regrettable.
お気は済んだ？
Have you had enough?
下がれ 下がれ
Step back, step back!
くだらね
How worthless.
ほら正気 戻っていっちゃった
Look, sanity has slipped away,
具体像 知っちゃっていいからさ
it's fine if you find out the concrete form.
レストインピースでご愁傷
Rest in peace, my condolences.
そんで来世で会おう See you again!
And let's meet in the next life, see you again!
うわぁ！
Whoa!
びっくりした、あぶなっ！
That scared me! Watch out!
危ないんじゃないですか？
Isn't that dangerous?
何、その動き。お前、ダンサー？
What's with those moves? Are you a dancer?
え？ダンサーですけど
Huh? Yes, I'm a dancer.
ふーん
Hmm...
私も！
Me too!
ダンサーです！
I'm a dancer!
え？なんか、すごいダンサーがいっぱい出てきた
What? A bunch of cool dancers suddenly showed up!
ていうか、なんか、ハジメちゃん、さっきダンサーのオーディション落ちちゃってさ
Anyway, Hajime just failed her dancer audition...
もしかして、あそこのシアターですか？
Wait, is it at that theater over there?
え、そう！
Yes, exactly!
え！それ、私も落ちました！
No way! I failed that one too!
えええ！え！私も！私も！私も！
What?! Me too! Me too! Me too!
みんな、落ちた仲間？
So we're all fellow rejects?
うん！
Yeah!
ねぇ、あのミニ番長審査員、センスないよね！
Right? Those mini-delinquent judges have zero taste!
わかる！ ほんとそれ！ ありえないよね！
I know, right?! Totally! Unbelievable!
うちらのダンス、ちゃんと見せつけてやろうじゃん！
Let's show them what our dancing is really made of!
おー！
Yeah!
もう、壁とは踊らないぞ！沙花叉クロエ！
I won't dance with walls anymore! Sakamata Chloe!
3メートルの覇気、水無瀬すう！
With 3 meters of Haki, Minase Suu!
カオスに落ちる、ハコス・ベールズ！
Falling into chaos, Hakos Baelz!
宇宙一の番長になる、轟はじめ！
The number one delinquent in the universe, Todoroki Hajime!
よし、うちらの始まりは...
Alright, our beginning starts...
こっから！
...from here!
Hey! Boy!
平凡にborn in the ニッポン 産声オギャー 行く先は荒野
Born ordinarily in Japan, first cry "ogyaa," heading to a wasteland.
ノーマル以下が 如何にして 地下深く眠る鉱脈掘れますか？
How can someone below average dig up ore veins sleeping deep underground?
知るか！伸びるか反るかしかねぇ この世の中 確かな価値観など無価値か
Who cares! In this world, it's make or break. Are solid values worthless?
カットなったってこの葛藤で 生まれたtakeはcutできんyo
Even if you lose your temper, you can't cut the take born from this conflict.
I can't be someone else, so I know, I know
このブレーキを壊したいの したいの
I want to break this brake, I want to.
これだけじゃやれねぇって分かってる
I know I can't make it with just this,
でもこれしかねぇからこれにかかってる
but this is all I have, so everything depends on it.
間違ってる未来でも俺には光ってる
Even if the future is wrong, it shines for me.
Let it fire!
燃やすこの闘志 その鉄格子
Burn this fighting spirit, break down that iron cage.
ぶち壊しどうしようもないままが
Breaking it down, just as I helplessly am,
自分なんだ こっから始まんだ
that is who I am. It starts from here!
いつかの童心もって努力し 夢と相思相愛になれるはずなんだ
With that childhood heart and hard work, I should be able to fall in love with my dreams.
こっから、こっから始まんだ
From here, it starts from here!
1-2-3-4 順番通り 行ってないだけで予定通り
1-2-3-4, not going in order, but still just as planned.
ローリン ローリン 転がってけ
Rollin', rollin', keep on rolling.
よりどりみどりの一生
A life full of endless choices.
1-2-3-4 順番通り 行ってないだけで予定通り
1-2-3-4, not going in order, but still just as planned.
ローリン ローリン 転がってけ yo
Rollin', rollin', keep on rolling, yo.
こっから始まんだ
It starts from here!
Ayy こっから？どっから？わからんだって燃料自体はすっからかん
Ayy, from here? From where? I don't know, since the fuel itself is completely empty.
こらアカンわ 楽観し 簡単にゃ済まぬまさに難関
This is bad, being optimistic. It won't end easily, it's truly a barrier.
一人になりたくても人だらけ さらけ出すにも一苦労なわけ
Even if I want to be alone, it's full of people. Barely showing myself is a real chore.
聞かれたくないサイレン ピーポー でもどこ行ったって「人・人・人」
I don't want to hear the sirens, people. But wherever I go, it's "people, people, people."
黄色信号でずっと進行
Always moving forward on a yellow light,
辛抱した先は歩こうぜレッドカーペット
and after enduring it, let's walk the red carpet.
タッリラッリラッリラッタ Come on!
Tarira-rira-rira-tta, come on!
よりどりみどりってさっき言ったろ？
Didn't I just say it's full of choices?
明日ありと思う心の仇桜
The fleeting cherry blossoms of a mind that assumes tomorrow will come.
生きてることが青天の霹靂
Just being alive is a bolt from the blue,
しかし悔しさで黒く燃える腹ん中
yet my inside burns black with frustration.
燃やせ 燃やせ 燃やせ
Burn it, burn it, burn it!
燃やすこの闘志 その鉄格子
Burn this fighting spirit, break down that iron cage.
ぶち壊しどうしようもないままが
Breaking it down, just as I helplessly am,
自分なんだ こっから始まんだ
that is who I am. It starts from here!
いつかの童心もって努力し 夢と相思相愛になれるはずなんだ
With that childhood heart and hard work, I should be able to fall in love with my dreams.
こっから、こっから始まんだ
From here, it starts from here!
One, two, three, let's go!
Check out the bridge!
俺 悪くない 何も間違ってない 自分じゃない 何かのせいにしたい 天才じゃないの 脱落しなさい
I'm not in the wrong, I made no mistakes. It's not me, I want to blame it on something else. If you're not a genius, then drop out.
これ フィクションじゃない よく見なさい 天分の才能などない でも
This isn't fiction, look closely. I have no natural talent, but...
やめられない 見たい あたしアホか バカみたい
I can't stop, I want to see. Am I an idiot? It's like I'm a fool.
限界 ここから ぬるい未来 メラメラ まだまだ 自分では 決めつけんな
From here, the limit, a lukewarm future, flaring up, there's still more. Don't make the decision yourself!
限界 探せよ お前らの 正解 本当の自分なんて いやしねえよ
Find your limits, your correct answer. There's no such thing as your "true self" anyway!
輝かなきゃ ダメ 響かなくちゃ ダメ と思い込んでることこそが
If I don't shine, it's no good. If it doesn't resonate, it's no good. Believing that very thing is...
好きこそ ものの上手なれ で 手突きこそ 終える根競べ
What one likes, one will do well. And next time, we'll finish this battle of endurance.
I can be someone else, I know, I know
Another wreck, 明日はしたいの したいの
Another track, tomorrow I want to do it, I want to do it.
足の向くままに動け
Move as your feet take you.
道なき道ほど進め
Advance all the more on pathless roads.
騙し騙し 魂なるねんだ Let's fire!
By fooling around, it will become my soul! Let's fire!
燃やすから闘志 そんだけ少し ぶち壊す闘志 用もないままが自分なんだ
Because I'll burn my fighting spirit, just that little bit, destroying fighting spirit, being useless is who I am.
ここから始まるんだ
It starts from here!
一生の闘志 持ってって努力 夢と相思相愛 になれるはずなんだ
Take your fighting spirit and make an effort. We should be able to fall in love with our dreams.
ここから ここから始まるんだ
From here, from here it starts!
1 2 3 4 順番通り 言う通りに動くだけのデストロイ
1, 2, 3, 4, in order, just moving as told, as expected.
Rolling Rolling 転がってけよ
Rolling, rolling, roll on!
Jolly Jolly 身の程の一生
Jolly, jolly, a life within my means.
1 2 3 4 順番通り 言う通りに動くだけの手通り
1, 2, 3, 4, in order, just moving as told, following the path.
Rolling Rolling 転がってけよ
Rolling, rolling, roll on!
ここから始まるんだ
It starts from here!
数年後 - a few years later -
A few years later...
Ha-ah ha-ah, Ha-ah ha-ah
I can't see what's behind those eyes
Just wait, talk a little before they're right
誰かの理想像に 耳を傾けてしまったの
I ended up listening to someone else's ideal image.
I can't take it back no more, I guess it's too late to call it off
I can't take it back anymore, I guess it's too late to call it off.
感情の無い世界に 溺れてさ
Drowning in an emotionless world...
Tell me who I'm supposed to be, I'm lost without your honesty
I'm stuck between yes and no, don't let me down
This is what you came for
狂ったように舞いな 舞いな
Dance like crazy, dance, dance!
Said you wanna be a superstar, so show me you won't break and fall apart
Take me higher, higher, show me you won't break and fall apart
Ha-ah ha-ah, Ha-ah ha-ah
Take me higher, higher
Show me you won't break and fall apart
何かを言おうとして
Trying to say something,
間違い探しの明日へと合図
an error-finding start signal.
Why's everybody's eyes on me?
Why is everybody's eyes on me?
慣れてしまうものね 視線の的<
I guess I get used to being the center of attention.
I can't take it back no more, I guess it's too late to call it off
I can't take it back anymore, I guess it's too late to call it off.
感じるプレッシャーは 押し殺してさ
Killing the pressure I feel...
Tell me who I'm supposed to be, I'm lost without your honesty
いい子気取りじゃ no no no, don't let me down
Acting like a good kid is a no-no-no, don't let me down.
This is what you came for
狂ったように舞いな 舞いな
Dance like crazy, dance, dance!
Said you wanna be a superstar, so show me you won't break and fall apart
Take me higher, higher, show me you won't break and fall apart
Ha-ah ha-ah, Ha-ah ha-ah
Take me higher, higher
Show me you won't break and fall apart
Yeah, said you wanna be a superstar, so show me what you got
I can't take it back no more, I guess it's too late to call it off
I can't take it back anymore, I guess it's too late to call it off.
感情の無い世界に 溺れてさ
Drowning in an emotionless world...
Tell me who I'm supposed to be, I'm lost without your honesty
I'm stuck between yes and no, don't let me down
This is what you came for
狂ったように舞いな 舞いな
Dance like crazy, dance, dance!
Said you wanna be a superstar, so show me you won't break and fall apart
Take me higher, higher, show me you won't break and fall apart
Set me higher, higher...
Show me your...
わあ！
Wow!
みんなー！
Everyone!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
仲間と励まし合って...
Encouraging each other with my friends...
みんなから勇気をもらって...
and getting courage from everyone...
こうしてステージに立って、たくさんの人の前でパフォーマンスすることができました！
I was able to stand on stage like this and perform in front of so many people!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
そしてなんと、Xのトレンド1位！
And what's more, we ranked #1 on X trend!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
そしてチャンネル登録者様も、120万人様にいったみたいで
Also, it seems my channel subscribers have reached 1.2 million!
本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so, so much!
わあ、嬉しい！
Wow, I'm so happy!
こうしてね、こう夢を追いかけて上京して...
Like this, chasing my dreams and moving to Tokyo...
こう、たくさんの人のスターになることができました！
and... I was able to become a star to so many people!
届き始める...
Starting to reach them...
まあでもね、この物語を作ることになって...
But you know, with creating this story...
たくさんの素敵なアーティストちゃんの楽曲をお借りして...
borrowing songs from many wonderful artists...
あの、作ることができたので...
we were able to build this...
本当にありがとうございました！
so thank you very much!
はじめも曲をたくさん作れるように頑張ります！
Hajime will also do her best to create many songs!
そして、これがはじめの100万人記念の新衣装になります！
And this is Hajime's new outfit for the 1 million celebration!
衣装の名前は「プラウドオード」衣装です！
The outfit's name is the "Proud Ode" outfit!
市原達矢さんに仕立てていただきました！
Tatsuya Ichihara tailored it for me!
はじめ...
Hajime...
皆さん応援してくれたおかげです、ありがとうございます！
It's all thanks to everyone's support, thank you!
今回の新衣装は...
About this new outfit...
髪がロング！
Long hair!
そして、足がなんか...
And my legs are somehow...
すごく長く見えるデザインで...
designed to look extremely long...
ほら、セクシーな美脚！
Look, sexy, beautiful legs!
で、皆さん何かおかしくない？
But everyone, isn't something weird?
ぴょこぴょこがない！
My hair-wiggles are gone!
嘘だ！そんなバカな！そんなバカな！
No way! That can't be! That can't be!
ぴょこぴょこがないだとう？！
My hair-wiggles are gone?!
うわ、嘘です！ぴょこぴょこもありまーす！
Wow, just kidding! They're still here!
まあぴょこぴょこないと、脳みそ出ちゃうからね！
Well, if I don't have them, my brains will spill out!
必要だよね！
They're necessary, right?
であと、ジャケットも脱げます！
Also, I can take off my jacket!
ほら！
Look!
ほら、セクシー！
Look, sexy!
詳しくはこの後のメン限で紹介するので、気になる方は見に来てください！
I'll show the details in the members-only stream after this, so please check it out if you're interested!
え、続いてなんと、新曲を披露しようと思います！
And next, I'd like to perform my new song!
皆さん、盛り上がる準備できてますかー？！
Is everyone ready to get hyped?!
おー！
Oh!
ロング可愛い？ありがとう！
Long hair looks cute? Thank you!
とてもね、かっこよくて、なんかセクシーな感じの曲になってるので
It's a very cool and somewhat sexy song,
ぜひ聴いてください！
so please listen to it!
それでは、行きます！
Here we go!
Deep Dive！
Deep Dive!
late night 今夜は with my girlies
Late night, tonight with my girlies
baby すぐ出な よ
Baby, come out right away
(let's get party, yeah)
(Let's get the party started, yeah)
頭から つま先 キメ てる lips
From head to toe, with styled lips
okay, ma ladies I need you to show me
Okay, my ladies, I need you to show me
wow マジ gorgeous, thanks...
Wow, seriously gorgeous, thanks
you look so badass
scream, scream, scream and shout ay
(scream, scream, scream and shout)
wow マジ gorgeous, thanks...
Wow, seriously gorgeous, thanks
you look so badass
scream, scream, scream and shout ay
turn it up now let go
Turn it up now, let's go
me and my girls, me and my girls 見て よ
Me and my girls, me and my girls, look at us
we're amazing, we are so amazing...
me and my girls, me and my girls ここから
Me and my girls, me and my girls, from here on
dive
yes, I'm a hot queen
dive, let's deep dive, I wanna deep dive
dive, yeah deep dive, ay, ay, ay
dive, yeah deep dive, yeah, yeah, yeah
let's get out of control
Girl, you look like that girl
Mind is also hot
My sunny queen, hot queen, hot queen
Girl, you look like that girl
Mind is also hot
My sunny queen, hot queen, hot queen
ワンストローク で star, glow
With one stroke, the star glows
bare minimum でも hard core
Even with the bare minimum, it's hardcore
ネイル 光って so shiny
Nails glowing, so shiny
マスカラ して I'm burning
Mascara on, I'm burning
髪 down？ それとも pony？
Hair down? Or a ponytail?
ooh-la-la ooh-la-la
視線 を control
Control their gazes
I don't mind them
誰か の approval
Someone's approval
I don't need it at all
wow マジ gorgeous, thanks...
Wow, seriously gorgeous, thanks
you look so badass
Gimme, gimme show time
Turn it up now
Make up!
Are you ready? Are you ready, ready go?
Are you ready? Are you ready, ready go!
Me and my girls... Me and my girls...
We gotta, we gotta, we gotta, we gotta...
Classic, classic...
Let's get back to beat, You're my hot queen!
Let's get back to the beat. You're my hot queen!
Dive, let's deep dive! I wanna deep dive!
Dive, your deep dive! Eh, eh, eh!
Dive, your deep dive! Let's get it, let's get it on!
Girl, you look like that, girl
マジ yoso hot hot
Seriously, so hot, hot!
まさに queen, hot queen, hot queen
Truly a queen, hot queen, hot queen!
Girl, you look like that, girl
マジ yoso hot hot
Seriously, so hot, hot!
まさに queen, hot queen, hot queen
Truly a queen, hot queen, hot queen!
Guns of Saxophone
[Song: Guns of Saxophone]
はい、ということで！生誕グッズが出ました！
All right! And with that, my birthday merch is out!
轟はじめ誕生日記念2026！フルセットはこんな感じです！
Todoroki Hajime Birthday Celebration 2026! The full set looks like this!
1つずつ紹介していきまーす！
I'll introduce them one by one!
1つ目！ぶんぶん番長アクリルスタンド！
First up! The Bunbun Bancho Acrylic Stand!
イラストはA5き先生に描いていただきました！
The illustration was drawn by A5ki-sensei!
台座が2つあるので、座ってる風にも、机などに引っかけるアクリルスタンドとしても使えます！
Since it has two bases, you can display her sitting, or use it to hang on your desk!
怒っているのがポイントです！
The highlight is her angry expression!
2つ目！はじめとおそろいチョーカー！
Second! The matching choker with Hajime!
はじめの新衣装とおそろいのチョーカーです！星のチャームが可愛い！
It's the same design as the choker in my new outfit! The star charm is so cute!
首のサイズが合わないよという方は、おカバンなどに付けてください！
If the neck size doesn't fit you, you can attach it to your bag instead!
3つ目！BANCHOジャージ！
Third! The BANCHO Tracksuit!
裏面のイラストはおもちチャウダーちゃんに描いていただきました！
The illustration on the back was drawn by Omochi Chowder-chan!
表面は刺繍になってます！スバル先輩の生地がとても良かったので同じのにしていただきました！
The front is embroidered! I loved the material of Subaru-senpai's, so we used the same!
最後！ぬいぐるみキーホルダー ブラックオーロラ衣装ver.！
And lastly! The plushie keychain, Black Aurora Outfit ver.!
初めて出した人気のぬいぐるみの、新衣装バージョンです！
This is a new outfit version of the popular plushie we released before!
あの時買えなかったよという方、ぜひお迎えしてください！
If you couldn't get it back then, please take this chance to bring her home!
そして、フルセット特典はこちら！
And here is the bonus for purchasing the full set!
今回のライブのチケット風カード！全員に直筆サイン書かせていただきます！
A ticket-style card for this live! I'll hand-sign every single one of them!
去年のライブでたくさんグッズを買っていただいたおかげで…
Thanks to everyone who bought so much merchandise at last year's live...
今年もこんなに力を入れることができました！ありがとうございます！
I was able to put this much effort into it again this year! Thank you so much!
今回のライブも楽しんでいただけるだろうか…
I hope you are enjoying today's live as well...
記念にグッズもお迎えしていただけると、今後の励みになります！
If you get some merch to remember today, it'll really motivate me for the future!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you so much!
以上、グッズ紹介でしたー！
And that's all for the merch intro!
あー、しんどかった！
Phew, that was exhausting!
この後、ラストスパート！
Up next is the final stretch!
一緒に盛り上がっていってください！いきますよー！
Keep the energy up and let's go wild! Here we go!
いぇーい！
Yeah!
Wow!
えええおおお！
Yeah! Oh!
わー！
Wow!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you, everyone!
はぁ...みんなありがとうございました！
Phew... Thank you so much, everyone!
それでは今回のライブに携わってくださった方をご紹介していきたいと思います！
Now, I would like to introduce the people who helped with this concert!
まずはダンサー、ゆににゃん！
First up, our dancers: Yuninyan!
ちよりゃん！
Chiyoryan!
みなみゃん！
Minamyan!
とろにゃん！
Toronyan!
ありがとう！そしてこの場にはいないんですけど、振付師のMiU先生、
Thank you! Also, though they aren't here right now, my choreographers: MiU-sensei,
Chisato先生！
Chisato-sensei,
タップの、Ayaka先生！
Ayaka-sensei for tap dancing,
ポッピンの、TODO先生！
TODO-sensei for popping,
ダンス監修、YUKA先生！
YUKA-sensei for dance supervision,
ボーカル監修、Maria先生！
and Maria-sensei for vocal supervision!
そしてゲストにお越しいただきました、
We also had guests join us:
星街すいせいちゃん、
Hoshimachi Suisei-chan,
博衣こよりちゃん、
Hakui Koyori-chan,
一条りりかちゃん、
Ichijou Ririka-chan,
りぐらすちゃん、
and the ReGLOSS members!
本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
そして今見えない中で稼働してくださっているスタッフの皆さん！
Also, the staff members who are working hard behind the scenes!
そして、はじめの目の前にいてくれてる、
And to everyone who is here right in front of Hajime,
見てくれている、見てくれた皆様、本当にありがとうございました！
and everyone who is watching or watched this, thank you so much!
それでは、ちょっと新曲について詳しくご紹介したいなと思います！
Now, I'd like to share some more details about my new song!
改めてタイトルは...
Once again, the title is...
ディープダイブ！
Deep Dive!
はい！
Yes!
MV公開はこの配信のすぐ後です！
The MV release is right after this stream!
音源リリースは本日24時からになります！
The song will be released on streaming platforms starting at 24:00 today!
皆さんたくさん聴いていただけると嬉しいです！
I'd be really happy if everyone listens to it a lot!
はぁ...それではここで重大発表いきたいと思います！
Phew... Now, it's time for a major announcement!
こちらの動画をご覧ください！
Please take a look at this video!
コラボ決定!!
[Collaboration Decided!!]
COMING SOON!!
わー！すごーい！
Wow! Amazing!
この度はじめとFILAちゃんのコラボが決定しましたー！
This time, a collaboration between Hajime and FILA has been officially decided!
うわー、嬉しい！ありがとうございます！
Wow, I'm so happy! Thank you so much!
そして、なんとスニーカーを含むアパレルをプロデュースさせていただきました！
And unbelievably, I got to produce apparel including sneakers!
やったー！
Yay!
はじめっぽいカラーリングを取り入れながら、
While incorporating colors that feel like Hajime,
男性でも女性でも似合うように意識してデザインしてみました！
I designed them carefully so they look great on both men and women!
一足目は、はじめのこだわりを詰め込んだスニーカーにしていくので、
The first item will be a pair of sneakers filled with things I'm picky about,
続報を楽しみにしていてください！
so please look forward to further updates!
え、そして、今回なんとあの、スニーカーだけじゃなくてね、
And this time, not just sneakers,
ジャージと、Tシャツと、キャップも、プロデュースしました！
I also produced tracksuits, T-shirts, and caps!
え、さらに、コラボにあたって、オリジナルのコラボロゴを、
Furthermore, for this collaboration,
FILAちゃんと、作りました！ドドン！
we made an original collab logo together with FILA! Ta-dah!
わー！かわいい！
Wow! So cute!
実はこのね、ロゴ、FILAちゃんと一緒に打ち合わせをして考えました、はじめ。
Actually, Hajime came up with this logo during meetings with FILA.
あ、こう、こういう感じにね、実際に手書きをしながら打ち合わせをして、
Like this, we had meetings while actually drawing by hand,
どの色がいいかなって、色んな色味を出してもらって、これに決めました！
discussing which colors would be best, and chose this after looking at various shades!
一目でね、はじめだって分かる、
I thought it'd be great to have
ミニ番長のシルエットがいいかなと思って入れてみました！
the silhouette of Mini Bancho so you can tell at a glance it's Hajime!
え、このロゴがね、コラボの商品にもつきます！
And this logo will also be featured on the collaboration items!
楽しみにしといてね！
Please look forward to it!
実はね、アパレル以外にもFILAちゃんとのコラボ商品が出ますので、
Actually, there will be collaboration items with FILA other than apparel,
皆さん、詳細な情報が出るのをぜひお楽しみに、お待ちください！
so please look forward to more detailed information!
え、この後ですね、メンバー限定アンコールライブ、21時15分からありますし、
And after this, we have the member-only encore live starting at 21:15!
この新曲についても色々詳しく見ていければと思いますので、
I'd also like to go over more details about this new song there,
ぜひまだの方は、チャンネル登録と通知をオンにして、
so if you haven't yet, please subscribe and turn on notifications,
メンバーも入っていただけると、
and maybe even join the membership!
アンコールも一緒に楽しめてハッピーだなと思います！
I think we'll have a happy time enjoying the encore together!
え、おさらいをすると、
To recap...
新曲MV、この後すぐ公開！
The new song's MV is releasing right after this!
え、21時からグッズ販売！
Goods sales start at 21:00!
21時15分からアンコールライブ！
The encore live starts at 21:15!
24時、新曲音源リリース！
And the digital release of the new song is at 24:00!
ありがとうね！
Thank you!
それでは、メンバーアンコールライブでお会いしましょう！
Then, let's meet at the member-only encore live!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
いっぱいコメントありがとう！
Thank you for all the comments!
嬉しかった！
I was so happy!
あ、ありがとう！
Ah, thank you!
いつもぱめと楽しいを共有してくれてありがとう！
[Letter: Thank you for always sharing fun times with me!]
みんなが期待してくれてるからもっとがんばりたい！もっと成長したいって思えるよ！
[Because everyone expects so much from me, it makes me want to work harder and grow even more!]
これからの歩みを守ってくれてありがとう❤
[Thank you for watching over my steps forward ❤️]
これからも楽しいをたくさん共有していきたいです！
[I want to continue sharing many fun times with you from now on!]